我们实际上仍然没有插入天气数据到ContentProvider
We're still not actually inserting
weather data into the ContentProvider.
所以 这个是一个好时机说说BulkInserts(BulkInsert是ContentProvider的一个方法)
So, this is a good time to
talk about BulkInserts.
记住 这个BulkInsert允许我们插入多行(数据)
Remember, that BulkInsert allows
us to insert multiple rows
比使用数据库事物更加高效
far more efficiently by using
a database transaction.
当我们需要插入14天的天气数据到数据库表中的时候
We can apply this when we need to
insert 14 days worth of weather data
我们可以使用它(BulkInsert)
into the table.
使用ContentProvider来批量插入内容数据到
Use the ContentProvider to BulkInsert
the vector of content values into
数据库
the database.
注意 在这个区域下方有几行提示 在你添加BulkInsert代码后
Note, there are a few lines underneath
the area where you add your BulkInsert
使用那些代码来测试显示你插入后的数据
code that you can use to test displaying
the values you just inserted.
那些代码会从数据库中读出这些数据 为他们创建ContentValues(ContentProvider的专用数据集合)
It will read those values out of
the data base, create content values for
和传给我们已经有的显示方法
them, and pass them into the same
display function we already have.